Hello.
こんにちは
Good day.
かんにちわ
It's cute.
かわいいね
It's not cute.
かわいくないです
thank you.
よろしくお願いします
I'll hold an audition for records.
記録用に オーディションなんて とるね
please.
お願いします
nice.
いいね
It's cute.
かわいいね
It's not cute.
かわいくない
Are you nervous?
緊張してる?
Just a little bit.
ちょっとだけ
Could you please take a moment to introduce yourself?
ちょっとじゃあ 自己紹介してもらおうかな
yes.
はい
This is Natsuki from my 3rd life.
3人生の なつきです
He will be 2 years old next year.
来年、2歳になります
oh.
おー
You're young.
若いね
Even the name.
名前までね
I was told that.
教えてもらいましたけど
I see.
そっか
Is school fun?
学校は楽しい?
It's fun.
楽しいです
Do you have any club activities?
なんか、部活とかやってるの?
As for club activities, I play badminton.
部活は バトミントンやってます
That's right.
そうなんだ
nice.
いいね
Are you taking the exam next year?
来年は 受験か?
I'm a test taker.
受験生です
Isn't it quite difficult to study now?
今、勉強で結構大変なんじゃない?
Yes, it's difficult.
はい、大変です
I go to the library and work hard by myself.
図書館行って、1人で頑張ってます
Are you going to the library?
図書館行ってるの?
yes.
はい
Regional?
地域の?
Yes, that's right.
はい、そうです
oh.
おー
You're young.
若いね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Is that what you're doing right now?
なんか今、あれやってるんだっけ?
Like idol activities.
アイドル活動みたいな
Yes, I am currently an idol and underground idol.
はい、今、アイドル、地下アイドル活動やってて、
It's still an egg though.
まだタマゴなんですけど
I'm doing my best.
頑張ってます
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
Are you doing live shows?
ライブとかやってるの?
I only do a few live shows.
ライブは、ちょっとだけやってます
But I haven't done that yet.
でも、まだそんなやってないです
I want to sing and dance.
歌って、踊ってみたいな
yes.
はい
To.
へ ー
Well, can I go take a look?
そうなん、ちょっと見に行ってもいい?
Please do go.
ぜひ、行ってください
Oh, it's okay.
あ、いいんだ
I'll be waiting.
待ってます
Is there a handshake event or something?
握手会とかあんの?
There will also be a handshake event.
握手会もあります
Oh, it's like a Cheki party or something.
おー、なんかチェキー会とか
Yes, there is.
はい、あるんで
Various things, so let's interact with the fans.
い ろんな、じゃあ、ファンの方と交流するんだ
yes.
はい
Quite a lot?
結構多い?
Natsuki-chan, it has to be Natsuki.
なつきちゃん、なつきじゃなきゃ
that's right.
そうです
copper?
どう?
Um, there are many fans?
あの、ファンの方多い?
It's a lot, but there's still a bit more...
多いんですけど、ちょっとまだまだ、
We don't have enough, so everyone, please become a fan.
足りないので、 みなさん、 ファンになってください
It will be.
なるよ
please.
ぜひ
Because it's so cute.
こんな可愛いんだから
I see.
そうか
Being an idol, you know, love, etc.
アイドルだから、 あれだね、恋愛とか、
Can't you?
できない?
I can't do it.
できないですね
Just in case, is it no good?
一応、ダメなの?
No.
ダメです
Is there no one you like?
好きな人はいないの?
The person I like was there before.
好きな人は、前はいました
I'm not there right now.
今はいないです
Is it okay to say before?
前っていいの?
when?
いつ?
Live in the 1st year of junior high school
中学1年生く
lie.
らい
Have you ever dated a man?
男 性とお付き合いしたことある?
Yeah, once.
うん、一回
Ah, there it is.
あ、あるんだ
it is?
それは?
When?
いつなの?
That's how I found the person I love.
それが、 好きな人を実りました
fault.
あら
1st year junior high school student.
中学1年生
Did you confess your feelings when you were in the first year of junior high school?
中 学 1年 生 の 時、 告白を自分からしたの?
Ah, after I said that, it happened.
あ、言ってから、されました
Eh, classmate?
えー、同級生?
Yes, we are classmates.
はい、同級生です
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
How long have you been together?
どのくらい付き合ってたの?
About half a year.
半年くらい
Did it end soon?
すぐ終わっちゃった?
It's over.
終わっちゃった
But even half a year at that time isn't that short?
でも、その時期の半年でも、 そんな短くない?
It's long, isn't it?
長いよね?
It was long.
長かったです
Well, did you go on a date?
えー、デートした?
We went on a date.
デートしました
We went to the movie theater and the aquarium.
映画館と水族館に行きました
Ah, that seems like it.
あー、 らしいね
Looks like a student.
学生らしい
I saw a penguin.
ペンギン見た
I saw it.
見ました
It was cute.
可愛かった
Did you hold hands and have a kiss?
手繋いだして、 チューとかしたの?
Chew?
チュー?
Are you shy?
照 れてんの?
I did.
しました
Where did you do it?
どこでしたの?
At the other person's house.
相手のお家で
Did you go to the other person's house?
相手のお家行ったの?
Did you have parents?
親はいた?
I didn't have any parents.
親いなかったです
picture?
え?
Yes, it's a little unhealthy.
そう、ちょっと不健康だね
Is that Chu?
それ、チュー?
Just chew?
チューだけ?
We also hugged.
ハグもしました
Oh, did you hug me?
あ、ハグしたの?
I chewed it.
チューしました
Oh, chew and hug me.
あら、 チューしてハグして
Is that all?
それだけですか?
Maybe you've become an adult?
もしかして、 大人になっちゃった?
Seriously?
マジで?
Does that mean you made it to the end?
最後までしちゃったってこと?
I did.
しました
You're in the first year of junior high school, right?
中学1年生でしょ?
It's quite early.
結構早いね
Is that so?
そんなもん?
I agree.
そうだね
What was it like the first time?
どうだった最初に?
Since then?
それ以来は?
I haven't.
は、してないです
If it's only once.
1回だと
How many times did you meet that person?
その人とは何回したの?
Is the pain less so?
あんまり痛みもなくなってきた?
My face turned red...
顔赤くなって...
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
恥ずかしいね
Because stories like this are important.
こう いう話も 大事だから
Nice to meet you today.
今日は よろしくね
cute.
かわいい
It's cute.
かわいいね
Awesome.
すげえ
That's good.
いいよね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Do you have any costumes for when you are currently active?
今、活動してる時の 衣装とかある?
The costume is a uniform.
衣装は制服でやってます
It's a uniform.
制服なんだ
What kind of uniform?
どんな制服?
Like a sailor suit.
セーラー服みたいな
Is it close to this?
こういうのに近い?
yes.
はい
Take your time.
ちょっとじっくりさ
I have to take a picture.
撮らなきゃいけない
Are you used to the camera?
カメラは慣れてる?
Just a little bit.
ちょっとだけ
I'm nervous.
緊張します
Have you ever been photographed?
撮られたりとかもある?
there is.
あります
There is.
あるんだ
I'll loosen you up.
ほぐしてあげる
It's getting hard.
固くなってる
Are you going to have a handshake event?
握手会とかするんでしょ?
I will.
します
I'm used to doing it at all.
全然するの慣れたよね
My hands are so sweaty.
手汗すごいね
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
I'm sweating a lot.
すごい汗かいてる
My hands are small.
手がちっちゃい
a little bit.
ちょっと
Look.
ほら
Don't you understand this?
こいつわかんないか
It's like tying your hair.
髪を結ぶ感じで
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
There are also commercials.
CMとかあるじゃん
Massage.
マッサージね
Shall I give you a massage?
マッサージしよっか
Have you been touched here?
ここ触られたりした?
What is this?
何、こういうの?
Have you ever been touched like this?
こういう触られたりしたの?
Is it okay?
いいの?
Touch me.
俺触って
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
It's not embarrassing at all.
全然恥ずかしくないよ
I don't resist it at all.
全然抵抗しないだね
Are you excited?
ドキドキする?
Do you ever catch a glimpse of something like this?
こういうのチラッと見ちゃうことあるでしょ?
No.
ないです
On stage.
ステージで
There is, right?
あるでしょ?
do not have.
ない
What kind of uniform does the school wear?
学校はどんな制服なの?
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
good?
いい?
That's good.
いいよね
I don't hate it.
嫌がってないもんね
No.
ダメ
Have you ever touched it?
触ったことあるんでしょ?
Yeah.
うん
Boyfriend's.
彼氏の
Without saying anything.
何も言わずに
I don't like it.
嫌だ
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
copper?
どう?
Touch it.
触ってごらん
It might be big.
大きいかも
Maybe it's big?
大きいかも?
I still don't know.
ちょっとまだ分かんないんですけど
That's amazing.
すごいな
What is this?
何これ?
That's amazing.
すごいね
Do you always wear underwear?
いつも下着なの?
Yeah.
うん
With your feet.
足で
Should I buy this underwear myself?
この下着は自分で買うの?
Is that so?
そうなの?
Where can I buy it?
どこで買うの?
I don't know.
分かんない
Maybe Shimamura.
島村とかかな
Don't you want something yourself?
自分でさ、 なんか、 欲しくなんないの?
It looks like I've tightened it up to this point.
ちゃんとここまで締めたような
wide.
広い
I want to wear some kind of adult-like underwear.
なんか大人っぽい下着履いてみたいとか
I might want to go buy some.
買いに行きたいかも
real?
ほ んと?
With my ex-boyfriend.
元彼とした
This is amazing.
すごいね、これ
Hey, raise your legs.
ちょっとさ、足さ、上げて
Open it firmly.
しっかり開いて
It's embarrassing.
恥 ず かしい
It was a woman.
女性だったの
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
Yeah.
うん
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
You also take photos like this, right?
こういう撮影もするでしょ?
In a group.
グループで
No way.
やだ
It's a little tight.
ちょっと締めてる
I haven't.
してない
Haven't you?
してない?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
What is it with my boyfriend?
彼氏とさ、 なんだっけ?
At home.
おうちで
Mas, what did you do?
マス、何したんだっけ?
I chewed.
チューした
Did you chew it?
チューした?
amazing.
すごい
Erotic.
エロい
Messed up.
めちゃくちゃ
You're an adult now.
もう大人だね
Not an adult.
大人じゃない
You're an adult now.
大人だよ、もう
So cute, Chikumi.
すごい可愛い、チクミ
What if I touch here?
ここ触るとどう?
tickles.
くすぐったい
tickles?
くすぐったい?
tickles.
くすぐったい
That's naughty.
やらしい
Do your best to come out.
頑張りつけ出して
Do it like this.
こう やって
Yes, it's naughty.
そう、やらしい
He looks naughty.
やらしい格好してる
That's naughty.
やらしい
It's a little tight.
ちょっと締めてる
Show me your pants.
パンツ見せてよ
I've already taken off my clothes so far.
もうここまで脱いでるんだから
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Look back a little.
ちょっと後ろ向いてごらんじゃん
Just like that.
そのまま
It's cute though.
可愛いんだけど
Let's take it off, then.
脱いちゃおうか、じゃあ
shirt.
ワイシャツ
Hey, aren't you bothering me?
ねえ、邪魔でしょ?
It's a big deal.
せっかくだけど
After all, you get to experience a lot of things.
もうね、 いろんなこと経験するんだからね
I'm not surprised.
びっくりしないよね
It smells a little sweaty though.
ちょっと汗臭いんだけど
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
Touch it.
触ってごらん
Did you do this for someone you like?
これは好きな人に やってあげた?
Haven't you done it?
やってあげてないの?
Because it makes me happy.
喜ぶから
You're good at it.
上手だね
You were wearing cute pants.
可愛いパンツ履いてたんだね
It's wide open.
しっかり開いてるし
Ah, amazing.
あ、すごい
It's spacious.
広いね
Will it be like this again?
こういう感じでまたある?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
There's no exhaust yet.
まだ排気ってないよね
Well then, more.
じゃあ、もっと
Oh, no.
あ、だめだよ
If I hide it.
隠したら
Awesome pink.
すっごいピンク
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
No.
だめだよ
Look.
ほら
Open it properly.
ちゃんと開いて
I can't see it yet.
まだ見えてないよ
In the end?
結局は?
When did you start coming here?
いつ頃から入ってきたの?
From junior high school students.
中学生から
After I became a junior high school student.
中学生になってから
It's still emerging.
まだ生えかけだよね
I licked it so hard.
すっごい舐めちゃった
Did you get licked?
舐められた?
Yeah.
うん
Just a little bit?
ちょっとだけ?
Yeah.
うん
Did you put your finger in?
指は入れられた?
Yeah.
うん